Xun Li

0444557114 | xunli253@gmail.com | Hobart www.linkedin.com/in/xunli-308715206

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Information Technology graduate with 2+ years of experience. I am looking to join a team with whom communication and teamwork are paramount. Having much experience working with JavaScript, I would jump at any opportunity to continue growing my skillset in the field of Full-Stack development.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

AMC Agency Aug 2021 - Mar 2022

Web developer internship, IT Department

Hobart

- Implemented web application with React, Typescript, HTML5, CSS3, SASS,
 JavaScript ES6, and responsive Web Design.
- Based on PostgreSQL, design database table.
- design and built up APIs to send and receive front-end data using Java and Spring Boot framework.
- Split the web page into independent components, and design reusable components.
- Use functional component and react Hook to implement reusable component.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Development

Mar 2022 - present

Team member Hobart

- Developed front-end project with React.js, Redux, HTML5, CSS, ES6, Sass and Responsive Design.
- Developed JR back-end project with Java, Node.js, JSON to export data tp various format.
- Utilised Postman, Trello and interactive mockup to aid devolopment, testing and documentation generation for JR projects.

Apr 2019 - Nov 2020

Team member Hobart

• Designed and built 2 web applications and 1 mobile application using React native

- Ensured the performance, quality, and responsivenens of 4+ applications
- Defined, designed, and shipped 5 new features
- Identified and corrected 100+ bug fixes
- Participated in code reviews to ensure code quality and receive mentoring from senior developers

EDUCATION

University of Tasmania

Feb 2019 - Dec 2020

Master of Information Technology

Hobart

High Distinction/Distinction achieved in Software Application Design and Implement, ICT System Strategy and Management, Enterprise Architecture and Systems, E-Logistics, Network Security Techniques and Technology, and Multi-perspective ICT Project.

SKILLS

Front-End:

Javascript ES6, Typescript, React, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Responsive Design, Flutter

Programming Language:

C#, Java, PHP, Dart

Database:

PostgreSQL, MySql, SQLite

Develops Tools:

Visual studio code, intelliJ IDEA, pgAdmine, GitHup, Postman